Guide to the Shu Lea Cheang Papers MSS.381
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Electronic Wiring Documentation and Promotional Flyer for Exit Art Show, 1990, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Cross Talk Book Projects and Desire Texts, 1990-1995 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Desire Shoot, Master, 1991-07-21 (Box 7, Hi8 381.0034, Hi8 381.0042)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Short Version and Shoot, 1991-1992 (Box 38, U-matic 381.0118)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Design (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Desire Project, Ass Shot Revised, Master ADO for Installation (Box 38, U-matic 381.0119)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Desire Edit Master (Box 38, U-matic 381.0120)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Desire Edit Master, cuid7030 (Box 38, Video cuid7030)
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Original format: 3/4" Umatic [Edit Master], Estimated Duration: 60 min.
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Desire Project, Ass Shot Revised, Master ADO for Installation, cuid7029 (Box 38, Video cuid7029)
  Original Format: 3/4" Umatic [Master], Estimated Duration: 30 min.
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- 1-900-Desires, circa 1992; cuid6030 (Box 7, Audiocassette cuid6030)
  Scope and Contents
  Tracks: 1. Larry Chua 2. bell hooks 3.Laurie Carlos 4. Renee Tajima 5. Jessica Hagedorn
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- 1-900-Desires (short version for MOMA), circa 1992; cuid6031 (Box 21, Audiocassette cuid6031)
  Tracks: 1. Laurie [Carlos] 2. Jessica Hagedorn 3. bell hooks 4. Larry Chua 5. Renee Tajima.
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- #2 Robbie, circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0124)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- #5 Cheryl, circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0125)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- #6 Maryann, circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0126)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) --#7 Shu Lea and Shu Lea Reprocessed, circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0127)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- #8 Rea, circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0128)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- #9 Pam, circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0129)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- #10 Pam (Second Tape) and Rea (Continued, Reprocessed), circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0130)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- #11 Beni, circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0131)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- #12 Rea (Reprocessed) and Coco (Printer), circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0132)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- #17 Yong Soon, circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0133)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- #19 Robin, circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0134)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Ass Film, circa 1992 (Box 39, Betacam 381.0135)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Reviews, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Lona Foote Production Stills, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Photographic Images, Promotional Material, and Press Clippings, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Press Clippings, Correspondence, and Financials, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Installation Diagrams, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Whitney Museum Exhibition, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Copy Proposal, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- Notebook, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992) -- 32 Rolls of Thermal Paper and original containers, undated (Box 42, Box 43)
  Gloves are required for handling. Care should be taken not to stress, crease, or fold the paper, as this could cause discoloration.
- Samples of Video Installations -- Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992); The Airwaves Project (1991); and Color Schemes (1989), circa 1992 (Box 39, Video 381.0154)
- Appointment Calendar, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Letter and Photographs re: Fall of the Berlin Wall, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Until Daybreak-Korea -- Exhibition Catalog, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Third World Newsreel -- Catalog, Promotional Booklets, 1992-1997 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Multiple Projects -- Work Files and Emails, 1992-1998; cuid28842 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_4)
- Tofu Assembly 1 + 2, 1993-04-19, 1993-04-27 (Box 21, Audiocassette 381.0058)
- Jane's Love Mess -- Audio Recording, 1993-06-13 (Box 6, Audiocassette 381.0009)
- Samples of Installations -- The Airwaves Project (1991) and Those Fluttering Objects of Desire (1992), 1993-12-02 (Box 39, Video 381.0153)
- To Enter (1993) -- New Museum (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Appointment Calendar, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Japan Fellowship -- Application, Information, Letters, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Indianapolis Center for Contemporary Art -- Exhibition Flyer, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Paris Exhibition -- Letter, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Video In Presentation, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Sex Fish (1993) -- Master (Box 11, Video 381.0046)
- Sex Fish (1993) -- Exhibition Copy, Dub Master, E.T. Baby Maniac, and Sex Bowl (Box 34, Video 381.0079)
- Sex Fish (1993) and Sex Bowl (1994) -- Video Recordings, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Video 381.0136 -- 381.0137)
- VNS Matrix -- Selected Articles, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Untitled Hi8 Video, 1994-06-25-1994-06-26 (Box 11, Video 381.0047)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- PMC -- Test -- Negative Film Reels, 1992-07-30; 381.0090 (Reel 381.0090)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Waste Land (Working Title), 1992-11-12-1992-11-13; 381.0092 (Reel 381.0092, Reel 381.0093, Reel 381.0094)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Waste Land (Working Title) Test, 1992-11-14; 381.0091 (Reel 381.0091)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Filming Negatives and Tests, 1992; 381.0162 (Reel 381.0162, Reel 381.0163, Reel 381.0164, Reel 381.0165, Reel 381.0166)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Script for Waste Land (Early Working Title), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Sea Wonder and Eco Cat, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Waste Land (Working Title) -- Filming Photographic Images, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 10-12, Box 15, Folder 1-2)
- Fresh Kill (1994), 1992-2024
  - Restoration, 2024
    - Release print
      - Reel one (Reel 381.0176)
      - Reel two (Reel 381.0177)
      - Reel three (Reel 381.0178)
      - Reel four (Reel 381.0179)
      - Reel five (Reel 381.0180)
    - Access files, cuid41200
      Derived from the adjusted DPX sequence and cropped to proper viewing aspect ratio.
    - Digital Cinema Package, cuid41201
      Specialized file package for cinema projection, derived from the adjusted DPX sequence and cropped to proper viewing aspect ratio.
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Nuki + Sushi (Working Title) Script, circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Whitney Museum Event Schedule, circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- 3rd Generation Seafood and Fulton Fish Market Location Reference Photographs, circa 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 5-7)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Al's Auto Location Reference Photographs, circa 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Blue Ribbon Fish Company Location Reference Photographs, circa 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- J + B Fish, Fulton Fish Market, and Lou's Market Location Reference Photographs, circa 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Jos. Carter Fish Dealers Location Reference Photographs, circa 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- KKKK Location Reference Photographs, circa 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Messing Fish Co. Location Reference Photographs, circa 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Research Photographs, circa 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Soap Factory Location Reference Photographs, circa 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Vione Fish Location Reference Photographs, circa 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Channel 4 Contract, Invoice, Budget, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Notebook with Plans and Filming Photographs, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- African Press, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- KKKK Music Archival Footage, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Musician Invoices and Contract, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Press Coverage, 1993-1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Designs (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Channel 4 Final Report (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Promotional Mailer and Movie Poster (Box 16, Folder 12, Box Shared Fales 073, Folder 1)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Script (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Film Still Photographic Images (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Taipei Golden Film Festival Catalog (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Master, Reels 1-5 (Box 37, Cassette 381.0107)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Sample Tape #2 (Box 39, Video 381.0138)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- KKKK Soundtrack, circa 1994 (Box 6, Cassette 381.0024)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- KKKK Soundtrack -- Reid / Active, circa 1994 (Box 21, Audiocassette 381.0059)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Press Coverage, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Images and Publicity Flyer, 1995-1997; cuid28843 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_5)
- Fresh Kill (1994) -- Event Program, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Sex Bowl (1994) -- Zinc Group -- Audio Recording, undated (Box 6, Cassette 381.0019)
- Sex Bowl (1994) -- #1, undated (Box 11, Video 381.0056)
- Sex Bowl (1994) -- Film to Tape Transfer, undated (Box 37, Video 381.0100)
- Mix 94 Cyber Queer, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Nicole Fernandez Correspondence, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- First Lesbian and Gay Parade in Tokyo -- Video Recording, 1994 (Box 6, Video 381.0008)
- First Lesbian and Gay Parade in Tokyo -- Scrapbook, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Second Annual Feminist Activism and Art Conference -- Press Clippings, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Japanese OK Girl -- Ephemera, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Multiple Projects -- Applications for Funding, Proposals, Emails, 1994-1995; cuid28844 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_6)
- Maria and Jam, Sex #1 -- Video Recording, 1995-01-04 (Box 7, Video 381.0036)
- Hanami, and Chu and Kayo Driving and Talk, 1995-04-12-1995-04-14 (Box 11, Video 381.0049)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Design, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Video Recordings, 1995-06-29 (Box 11, Video 381.0050 - 381.0051)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Walker Art Center Title Reel, 1995-10-14 (Box 39, Video 381.0140)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Script, Promotional Flyer (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Programming (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Photographic Slides (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Visual Materials from LaserDisc -- Master from AVID (Box 39, Video 381.0141)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Copy 2 with Superimposed Titles (Box 39, Video 381.0142)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Walker Art Center Exhibition Documentation (Box 39, Video 381.0143)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Video Recording (Box 39, Video 381.0144)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Walker Art Center Installation Documentation (Box 39, Video 381.0145 - 381.0147)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Budget, Contract, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Promotional Exhibition Brochure, Poster, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 4, Box 13, Folder 2)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Texts for Projections, Images, Expenses, and Proposals, 1995-1996; cuid28847 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_9)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Walker Art Center Promotional and Press Material, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Walker Art Center Installation Documentation, 1996 (Box 39, Video 381.0148)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- An Installation -- Documentation, Edit Master, circa 1994-1995 (Box 37, Video 381.0101)
- Bowling Alley (1995) -- Work Files, circa 1995 (Box 33, Disc FA_MSS_381_74 -- FA_MSS_381_76)
- Fingers and Kisses (1995) -- Sex Break, Lesbian Weekend Titles C+M V.O., circa February 15, 1995 (Box 11, Video 381.0053)
- Fingers and Kisses (1995) -- Voice with Kayo and Asami, 1995-05-10 (Box 7, Audiocassette 381.0027)
- Fingers and Kisses (1995) -- Voices (Box 6, Cassette 381.0020)
- Fingers and Kisses (1995) -- Video Recording (Box 39, Video 381.0139)
- Fingers and Kisses (1995) -- Film Packaging Graphics, cuid28848 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_10)
- Fingers and Kisses (1995) -- Agreements, Promotional Material (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Fingers and Kisses (1995) -- 4:15 Tokyo. Haranjuku / Train Kinswomyn. Stories + Kisses, circa 1995 (Box 11, Video 381.0055)
- Coming Home (1995) -- [Izumo] Marou and Claire [Maree] Bathtub Rehearsal -- Semi-Demi, 1995-02-06 (Box 7, Video 381.0037)
- Coming Home (1995) -- Bianfuda with [Izumo] Marou and Claire [Maree], 1995-02-09 (Box 11, Video 381.0048)
- Coming Home (1995) -- Bianfuda with [Izumo] Marou and Claire [Maree], undated (Box 39, Video 381.0122)
- Press Clippings, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Collaborative Project - Japan's Homeless Page of Disjointed Narrative and Connected Issues -- Images and Page Design, 1995; cuid28845 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_7)
- Awake Dreaming, A Cyber Blitz Jam Session -- Exhibition Design Material, 1995; cuid28846 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_8)
- Asia Edge Project, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Research File -- Patricia Williams Writings, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Elephant Cage Butterfly Locker (1996) -- Images, Work Files, and Emails, 1994-1997; cuid28849 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_11)
- Elephant Cage Butterfly Locker (1996) -- Installation Images, July-August 1996 (Box 20, Folder 3-5)
- Elephant Cage Butterfly Locker (1996) -- Notebooks -- Okinawa Project, Books #1 and #2 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
- Elephant Cage Butterfly Locker (1996) -- Pole Design Memo (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Elephant Cage Butterfly Locker (1996) -- U.S. Military Presence in Asia-Pacific Region Research (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Elephant Cage Butterfly Locker (1996) -- Okinawa Project -- Onaga Terminate Contract (Box 39, Video 381.0149)
- Elephant Cage Butterfly Locker (1996) -- Photographic Slide Images, circa 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Elephant Cage Butterfly Locker (1996) -- Installation Instructions, Budget, Contracts, Photographs, Press Clippings, Plans / Map, and Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 19, Folder 9, Box 20, Folder 1-2, Box 29, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 1)
- Elephant Cage Butterfly Locker (1996) -- Letter and Publication re: Cheang's Butterfly Banners, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Elephant Cage Butterfly Locker (1996) -- 1000 Memories Butterfly Banner, 1999 (Flat-file-folder 1)
- Curator / Dentsu Meeting, 1996-07-31 (Box 11, Video 381.0052)
- Photograph Album -- Trip, Attending Wedding, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Multiple Projects -- Work Files and Emails, 1996; cuid28850 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_12)
- Appointment Calendar / Address Book, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Notebooks -- Ideas, Notes, Contacts, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
- Escalita Shooting / Lady Catira Shoot -- Video Recording, 1997-06-16 (Box 6, Video 381.0010)
- Buy One Get One (1997) -- NTT InterCommunication Center (ICC) Biennial Exhibition Proposal and Images, 1996-2000; cuid28851 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_13)
- Buy One Get One (1997) -- NTT InterCommunication Center (ICC) Biennial Exhibition Photographs, Letter (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Buy One Get One (1997) -- NTT InterCommunication Center (ICC) Biennial Exhibition Video (Box 39, Video 381.0150)
- Buy One Get One (1997) -- NTT InterCommunication Center (ICC) Biennial Exhibition Promotional Material and Catalog, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 10, Box 23, Folder 1)
- Women and the Art of Multimedia (WAM) -- Speaker Lists, Speech Text, Event Schedule, circa 1997 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Harvard Internet Conference -- Information Packet, 1998-05-26-1998-05-29 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- With Scholars -- Video Recording, 1998-08-06 (Box 6, Video 381.0011)
- Research Files -- Chemical Castration and Child Pornography, 1998; cuid28852 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_14)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Japanese Magazine, circa 1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Peterson Trial, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Scripting Interventions, circa 1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Transsexuals in Prison Research, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Sketches, Plan for Production, 1992, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Press Clippings (dating 1897-1981) Research, 1992-1997 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- lambdaMOO Case, 1993-1996 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Court Documentation, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Research Press Clippings, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Falls City, Nebraska Research and Press Clippings, 1994-1995, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Transsexual Magazines, 1994, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Notebook with Notes and Ideas, 1994-1997 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- "DJ", "Jordy", and "Texas" Images, 1994-1998; cuid28853 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_15)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Photographs -- Courtroom, circa 1995 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Rockefeller Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Transsexual Research, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- NYFA Application, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Proposal, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Research, Edited Sounds, Webpages, Emails, and Proposal, 1996-1999; cuid28855 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_17)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- DJ Top Surgery, 1997-02-24 (Box 21, Minidv 381.0076 - 381.0077)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- DJ Top Surgery, 1997-02-24 (Box 39, Video 381.0151)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Research, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Project Update, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Budget, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Photograph Release Forms, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Storyboard Scripts, Notes, and Correspondence, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Wheatley Case, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 10-11)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Final Script, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Institute on the Arts and Civic Dialogue (IACD) Images, Proposal, Scripts, Press, Webpages, Rehearsal Schedule, and Contact Lists, 1997-1998; cuid28854 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_16)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Photographs, Notes, Research, and Schedules, 1997-1998, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Notebook, circa 1997-1999 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Palmer W. (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Guggenheim Museum (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Press, IACD (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Proposal, Research, Contacts, and Presentation Panel (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Virtual Court Test Trial (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Presentation, Information Sheet (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Transexualism Historical Research Press Clippings (Box 26, Folder 8-9)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Photographic Images, Press Clippings (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Press Clippings (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Script, Final (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Amsterdam Fund for the Arts -- Brandon Forum (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Art Institute of Chicago Contract (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Notes (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Cal Arts Application (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Press Clippings, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 1, Box 17, Folder 5)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Script Notes, 1998, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Essays on Transsexualism, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Clear Plastic Pills Containing Messages and Smaller Pills, undated (Box 41)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Trans Cast, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Aachen Panopticon Prison Images and Text Research, undated (Box 27, Folder 9, Box 17, Folder 6)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Conversation with Pet Williams and Liz Diamond Sound Recording, July 15, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 381.0028)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Panopticon, undated (Box 6, Video 381.0014)
- Brandon (1998-1999) -- Nebraska / Court, undated (Box 21, Video 381.0075)
- Work Files on Multiple Artworks -- Writings, Project Proposals, Letters, Photographic Images, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Multiple Projects -- Work Files and Emails, 1998-2000; cuid28856 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_18)
- Ota / Akiva -- Video Recording, 1999-08-06 (Box 6, Video 381.0012)
- Andes, New York Farm Garden -- Photographs, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Press Clipping Re: Cheang, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- HoME -- Images and Graphics, 1999-2000; cuid28857 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_19)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Tokyo Research Photographs, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Script Draft, Work Files, Graphics, Press, and Notes, 1997-2000; cuid28858 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_381_ER_20)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Notebooks, Photographs, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Chip Delany, Notes, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Notebooks, Publications, 1998-2000 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
- I.K.U. (2000) --ASAI, 1999-12-04 (Box 6, Video 381.0013)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Filming Photographs and Movie Promotional Material, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Sundance Film Festival, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Publications, Letters, Promotional Material, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Asai Takashi -- Full Screen Blow-up Upconversion Protection Master, 2000-01-20 (Box 37, Cassette 381.0102)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Asai Takashi -- Source Tape, 2000-01-21 (Box 37, Video 381.0103)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- with Mosaic, with Mask, 2000-01-24 (Box 37, Video 381.0104)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Woo Art International Video Recording, 2000-04-04 (Box 37, Video 381.0105)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Fantasia -- Breteiles 1.66 Video Recording, 2000-07-21 (Box 37, Video 381.0106)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Scripts, Notes, Photograph (Box 29, Folder 4)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Press Clippings (Box 29, Folder 7)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- 2nd Edit, circa 2000 (Box 6, Video 381.0006 - 381.0007)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Storyboards, undated (Box 29, Folder 8, Box 17, Folder 7)
- I.K.U. (2000) -- Shu Lea and Asai Contract Negotiation, undated (Box 6, Video 381.0023)
- Japanese Performers Promotional Material, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- NYC Proclamation -- MIX First Annual New York Lesbian and Gay Experimental Film and Video Festival of New York Day, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Civitella Ranieri -- Letters, Information/Promotional Booklets, 2000-2002 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Letters Re: Multiple Cheang Artworks, 2000, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Locker Baby Project (2001-2012) -- Script, Correspondence, Budget, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Locker Baby Project (2001-2012) -- Proposal Packet, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Kingdom of Piracy (2002) -- Correspondence, Proposal, Press Clippings, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Garlic=Rich Air (2002) -- Photographs, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 7)